Guide to the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Photographs PHOTOS 023 001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Contact Prints, 1940-1964
  - Charleston S.C. Softball Team, undated; 04532 (Box 9)
  - Charleston, undated; 04615 (Box 9)
  - Dade City, undated; 04640 (Box 9)
  - Arrow Mills Shop Meeting Houston, Texas, undated; 04824 (Box 9)
  - Houston D.P.O Arrow Mills Plant, undated; 04957 (Box 9)
  - Charleston D.P.O. meets Carolina State CIO, undated; 05297 (Box 9)
  - Baseball, undated; 05601 (Box 9)
  - Baseball, undated; 05602 (Box 9)
  - Memphis Local 19 Assorted Meeting Shots, undated; 05825 (Box 9)
  - Golding Social, Jun 8, 1940; 06100 (Box 9)
  - Golding Social, Jun 8, 1940; 06101 (Box 9)
  - Election Social ["Our goal 2500 members organized…", Jan 1940; 06200 (Box 9)
  - Social Hall, undated; 06300 (Box 9)
  - Unidentified convention or meeting, ca. 1940s?, undated; 07500 (Box 9)
  - Stewards, Oct 8, 1940; 07600 (Box 9)
  - Unidentified convention, ca. 1940s?, undated; 08100 (Box 9)
  - Medical Plan Outing Sponsored by E. Harlem Community Comm., undated; 09011 (Box 9)
  - Reitred Members at Hyde Park, undated; 10288 (Box 9)
  - Unidentified meeting, undated; 10300 (Box 9)
  - Jewish s Comm. Celebration of Israel, 13th Anniversary, undated; 10443 (Box 9)
  - Unidentified Social Event, undated; 11206 (Box 9)
  - Art Show Opening, Mar 18, 1964; 19142 (Box 9)
  - Robinson, Cleveland: Portraits, May 1964; 19153 (Box 9)
  - Retirees at City Hall on Fare Reduction Campaign, May 1964; 19157 (Box 9)
  - Art Show Winning Pictures, undated; 19160 (Box 9)
  - Unidentified, undated; 19206 (Box 9)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 9)
  - Allen, Vera (Local 78), undated (Box 9)
  - Baldins, Pete, undated (Box 9)
  - Bernknopf, Al, undated (Box 9)
  - Burke, Bob, undated (Box 9)
  - Brown, Al (Philadelphia District 76), undated (Box 9)
  - Bush, Harry, undated (Box 9)
  - Carnes, Nicholas, undated (Box 9)
  - Cayton, Revels, Apr 1948 (Box 9)
  - Dicker, Al, undated (Box 9)
  - Doswell, Morris, undated (Box 9)
  - Eisenberg, Bernard, undated (Box 9)
  - Gechter, Alice, undated (Box 9)
  - Hamilton, Henry, undated (Box 9)
  - Irsay, Leonard, undated (Box 9)
  - Kravity, Anne, undated (Box 9)
  - Kuntsch, Dick, undated (Box 9)
  - Lebold, Irving, undated (Box 9)
  - Letz, Esther, undated (Box 9)
  - Levine, Murray, undated (Box 9)
  - Livingston, David, undated (Box 9)
  - Loring, Marcella, undated (Box 9)
  - Mancheim, Phil, undated (Box 9)
  - Meisler, George, undated (Box 9)
  - Michelson, Bill, undated (Box 9)
  - Molofsky, Sol, undated (Box 9)
  - Murphy, Mary, undated (Box 9)
  - Nelson, Walter, undated (Box 9)
  - Nyitray, Florence, undated (Box 9)
  - O'Connor, Bill, undated (Box 9)
  - Osman, Arthur, undated (Box 9)
  - Osman, Harry, undated (Box 9)
  - Paley, Jack, undated (Box 9)
  - Pecci, Lou, undated (Box 9)
  - Portnoy, Bill, undated (Box 9)
  - Ravitch, Chas, undated (Box 9)
  - Reverby, Milton, undated (Box 9)
  - Rosenberg, Mollie, undated (Box 9)
  - Siegel, Morris, undated (Box 9)
  - Slatin, Leon, undated (Box 9)
  - Stein, Pete, undated (Box 9)
  - Sussman, Max, undated (Box 9)
  - Talkow, Bernie, undated (Box 9)
  - Thomas, W.E. (Red), undated (Box 9)
  - Tillem, Joe, undated (Box 9)
  - Turner, Abe, undated (Box 9)
  - Wacker, Leonard, undated (Box 9)
  - Wallant, Chas, undated (Box 9)
  - Wantman, Mac, undated (Box 9)
  - Warshaver, Herb, undated (Box 9)
  - Werner, Lou, undated (Box 9)
  - White, Frank, undated (Box 9)
  - Unidentified Portraits, undated (Box 9)
  - Unidentified Portraits, undated (Box 9)
  - Veteran 65ers, undated (Box 9)
  - Veteran 65ers, undated (Box 9)
- Series III: District 65 Divisions, undated
  - Apparel, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Apparel – Executive Board, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Apparel – Membership Meetings, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Apparel – Newly Organized, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Apparel – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Apparel – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Apparel – Social, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Button, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Button – Executive Board, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Button – Social, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Button – Industry Pictures, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Button – Membership Meetings, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Button – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Button – Newly Organized, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Button – Shop Meeting, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Chemical and Paint, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Chemical and Paint – Executive Board, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Chemical and Paint – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Chemical and Paint – Newly Organized, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Chemical and Paint – Shop Meeting, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Cigar, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Cigar – Executive Board, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Cigar – Industry Pictures, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Cigar – Membership Meetings, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Cigar – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Cigar – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Cigar – Social, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Corrugated NJ and NY, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Corrugated - New Jersey and New York – Executive Board, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Corrugated - New Jersey and New York – Industry Pictures, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Corrugated - New Jersey and New York – Membership Meetings, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Corrugated - New Jersey and New York – Newly Organized, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Corrugated - New Jersey and New York – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Corrugated - New Jersey and New York – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Cosmetic and Drug, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Cosmetic and Drug– Executive Board, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Cosmetic and Drug– Industry Pictures, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Cosmetic and Drug– Membership Meetings, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Cosmetic and Drug– Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Cosmetic and Drug– Newly Organized, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Cosmetic and Drug– Shop Meetings, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Cosmetic and Drug– Social, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Dental, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Dental – Executive Board, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Dental – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Dental – Membership Meetings, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Dental – Newly Organized, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Dental – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Dental – Social, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Direct Mail, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Direct Mail – Executive Board, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Direct Mail – Industry Pictures, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Direct Mail – Membership Meetings, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Direct Mail – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Direct Mail – Newly Organized, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Direct Mail – Social, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Display, undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Display – Executive Board, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Display – Industry Pictures, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Display – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Display – Social, undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Dry Goods, undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Dry Goods – Industry Pictures, undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Dry Goods – Membership Meetings, undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Dry Goods – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Dry Goods – Newly Organized, undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Dry Goods – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Dry Goods – Social, undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Dry Goods – Executive Board, undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Financial, undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Financial – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Food, undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Food – Executive Board, undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Food – Industry Pictures, undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Food – Membership Meetings, undated (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Food – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Food – Newly Organized, undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Food – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Food – Social, undated (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Garment Supplies, undated (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Garment Supplies – Executive Board, undated (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Garment Supplies – Industry Pictures, undated (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Garment Supplies – Membership Meetings, undated (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Garment Supplies – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Garment Supplies – Newly Organized, undated (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Garment Supplies – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Garment Supplies – Social, undated (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - General Office, undated (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - General Office – Executive Board, undated (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - General Office – Industry Pictures, undated (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - General Office – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - General Office – Newly Organized, undated (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - General Office – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - General Office – Social, undated (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Hardware, undated (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Hardware – Industry Pictures, undated (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Hardware – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Hardware – Newly Organized, undated (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Hardware – Membership Meeting, undated (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Insurance, undated (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Knitwear, undated (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Knitwear – Executive Board, undated (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Knitwear – Industry Pictures, undated (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Knitwear – Membership Meetings, undated (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Knitwear – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Knitwear – Newly Organized, undated (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Knitwear – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Knitwear – Social, undated (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Metal and Misc - Products, undated (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Metal and Misc - Products – Executive Board, undated (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Metal and Misc - Products – Industry Pictures, undated (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Metal and Misc - Products – Membership Meetings, undated (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Metal and Misc - Products – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Metal and Misc - Products – Newly Organized, undated (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Metal and Misc - Products – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Metal and Misc - Products – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Millinery, undated (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Millinery – Executive Board, undated (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Millinery – Industry Pictures, undated (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Millinery – Membership, undated (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Millinery – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Needle Processing, undated (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Needle Processing – Membership Meetings, undated (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Needle Processing – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Needle Processing – Newly Organized, undated (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Needle Processing – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - NJ Local, undated (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - NJ Local – Executive Board, undated (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - NJ Local – Industry Pictures, undated (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - NJ Local – Newly Organized, undated (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - NJ Local – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - NJ Local – Social, undated (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - News, undated (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - News – Executive, undated (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - News – Membership Meetings, undated (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - News – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - News – Newly Organized, undated (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - News – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Retail Misc, undated (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Retail Misc – Industry Pictures, undated (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Retail Misc – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Retail Misc – Newly Organized, undated (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Retail Misc – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Retail Misc – Social, undated (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Retail TV, undated (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Retail TV – Executive Board, undated (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Retail TV – Industry Pictures, undated (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Retail TV – Membership Meetings, undated (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Retail TV – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Retail TV – Newly Organized, undated (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Retail TV – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Retail TV – Socials, undated (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Revlon, undated (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Salesmen's Guild, undated (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Sample Card, undated (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Screen, undated (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - Screen – Executive Board, undated (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - Screen – Membership Meetings, undated (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - Screen – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Screen – Newly Organized, undated (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - Screen – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - Screen – Socials, undated (Box 4, Folder 162)
  - Shoe, undated (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - Shoe – Executive Board, undated (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - Shoe – Industry Photos, undated (Box 4, Folder 165)
  - Shoe – Membership Meetings, undated (Box 4, Folder 166)
  - Shoe – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - Shoe – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 4, Folder 168)
  - Shoe – Newly Organized, undated (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - Shoe – Socials, undated (Box 4, Folder 170)
  - Textile, undated (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Textile – Executive Board, undated (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Textile – Industry Pictures, undated (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Textile – Membership Meetings, undated (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Textile, undated (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Textile – Newly Organized, undated (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Textile – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Textile – Socials, undated (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Toy and Giftware, undated (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Toy and Gift – Executive Board, undated (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Toy and Gift – Industry Pictures, undated (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Toy and Gift – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Toy and Gift – Negotiations and Arbitrations, undated (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Toy and Gift – Newly Organized, undated (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Toy and Gift – Shop Meetings, undated (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Toy and Gift – Socials, undated (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Anti-Sales Tax Demonstration, undated (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Anti-Vietnam War Rally, undated (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Civil Rights, undated (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Club 65, undated (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Community Fund Drive, undated (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - David Livingston, undated (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - 1199, undated (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Emmett Till Rally, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Kfar Menachem, undated (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - Labor for Peace, undated (Box 5, Folder 196)
  - Medical Care, undated (Box 5, Folder 197)
  - Miscellaneous Historical, undated (Box 5, Folder 198)
  - Political Activities, undated (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Unemployment Activities, undated (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Union Members at Work, undated (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Union Voice Staff, undated (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - NP Modern prints from District 65 negative collection (arranged in neg, undated (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Snapshots of Leadership, undated (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Black Trade Unionist (Hidden Injuries Art Gallery, 1987), undated (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - Collection: Control Sheets, undated (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - 6th Biennial Convention (Atlantic City), 1954 (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - 6th Biennial Convention (Atlantic City), 1954 (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - 6th Biennial Convention (Atlantic City), 1954 (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - 6th Biennial Convention (Atlantic City), 1954 (Box 7, Folder 210)
  - 6th Biennial Convention (Atlantic City), 1954 (Box 7, Folder 211)
  - 6th Biennial Convention (Atlantic City), 1954 (Box 7, Folder 212)
- Series IV: Unprocessed Materials, undated
  - Box 31, undated
    Staff, organizers and administrator portraits, unidentified individual and group portraits, staff events, demonstrations, 1983 March on Washington and Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union 10th Anniversary. Badges, artifacts and slides.
  - Oversize Materials, undated (Box OS006, Folder 2)
    Civil Rights and Anti-Discrimination, Israel.
  - Civil Rights Photo Exhibit, 1960-1980 (Box 33, Folder 1-7)
  - Photographs, graphics, 1950-1980 (Box 34, Folder 1-6)